My lady,
they've all practiced in the morning,
and the escort is done.
You can have a rest this morning.
Come here.
I didn't do anything
too much to you last night, did I?
Nothing too much.
Then
what's wrong with your eyes?
My brother just came.
It doesn't matter.
Miss Tang Xin,
I was just about to look for you.
What's up?
Did you finish composing the piece so soon?
Yes, I did.
I'm eager to play it for you
and see if there's anything that needs tweaking.
What happened to your eyes?
It's nothing serious.
Let's go to my room.
Stop.
Come here.
You're not done getting Jiaojiao drunk yesterday,
and you even called Xin into your room.
Do you want another punch?
Brother.
Tang Xin and I were just working on the lyrics and music.
We didn't drink.
Besides, Jiaojiao was also in the room.
Brother,
you can't go on like this.
How about
I help you to pursue her?
I don't need it.
Come to my room tomorrow.
You can talk.
I'll go escort.
Have a good talk.
Ms. Tang.
Please.
How does it match your lines?
It's like a perfect match.
By the way, Tang Xin,
here you are.
I want to turn these stories
into scripts,
so the music
needs more changes.
Okay.
Jiaojiao,
am I your best friend?
Of course.
Then why didn't I know about these things?
How do you know?
You told me when you were drinking yesterday.
What?
Jiaojiao drank with you?
She doesn't remember anything after drinking.
You... you...
So you treat him as your mother.
I'm just going along with the act.
You can't use this in the final exam.
If you dare to say a word,
I...
I was even thinking
about having you act with me.
- That's great. - No way.
Jiao,
you've been to so many places.
You best sense the Yun State's prosperity.
I want to use your eyes
to see the peace and prosperity of the Yun State.
But...
How romantic!
I want to see it too.
Please.
Alright.
But can you let me think about it first?
The invincible little typhoon,
rush forward for love.
Once the deal is made,
sweet to the point of sadness.
This is the true love premiere edition,
With inside information.
There will be a surprise at the Nebula Conference.
Pay more attention.
That night,
my husband became my mother.
What dirty things are these?
Watching less makes it easy to dream.
Bro,
help me pursue Xin.
Are you really up to it?
I couldn't do it for ten years.
What can you do?
Bro.
It's been ten years.
You haven't made any progress.
You two are childhood sweethearts.
Ms. Tang must know
your character and temperament.
And the plectrum you gave her
shows you know her preferences.
Bro.
This is an excellent gift
and Ms. Tang Xin's preferences
to design this perfect gift.
It's guaranteed to work.
Of course,
there's also a trump card.
Here.
Don't open it yet.
When you see Ms. Tang Xin next
and don't know what to say,
then open it.
Read out loud what's written on it.
Just read a few words?
Is it that simple?
If you can't get her,
I'll let you do whatever you want.
But if you succeed,
you have to promise
you'll never hit me again.
Deal.
Tang Xin was right.
He's really going to a party.
Boss,
Are you going?
No.
I won't put on makeup for him,
nor wear clothes like Tang Xin.
I think
you're saying the opposite of what you mean.
Cut the crap.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
But the interest of Huayue Building is too high.
It's almost equal to the money we owe.
My Lord,
why do you help Grandpa repay the money?
The agency will pay the bill eventually.
It's better to repay it earlier.
Otherwise, the interest
will be higher and higher.
Well,
you go back to the agency first.
I have something to do.
Got it.
I knew it.
My Lord must have made preparations.
Go tell Gong Xi.
Miss,
these are the latest styles in Yunjing.
Try them on if you like.
I'm just looking around.
Shopkeeper,
put today's goods
in the back room.
Is this what you want to do?
It's good to make money by your own efforts.
Bai,
if you don't have a good time outside,
you can come back to the Escort Agency.
You called me here
just to show me
that you can clean up?
I... I...
What about your precious wood?
They're...
They're all put away.
Didn't you say you had something good to show me?
Hurry up.
I... I...
Forget it.
I...
like you.
No, no, no.
Well,
this is Cheng Qi.
He said...
Cheng Qi said this is
the trump card.
No.
No, I'm sorry.
I take it back.
That's not okay.
Su's Escort Agency always keeps its word.
What you said
can't be taken back.
You...
You agreed?
Put your wooden men back.
I'm not used to this.
Okay, okay.
I'll do as you say.
Jiao,
as you wish.
we love each other
and love each other deeply.
No matter how many veils she wears,
I can still recognize her.
I'm Su Yuejiao's husband.
My dear, my dear.
My dear.
Thank you, my dear.
I'm already married.
I'm the head of the Su's Escort Agency.
It's a deal.
You haven't told me about the banquet.
After so many years,
this agency hasn't changed at all.
Jiaojiao,
what do you think if I live here in the future?
It's good.
Your brother said he likes me last night.
I saw it.
If my father knows
I'm with the head escort's son,
he must be very happy.
My parents watched you grow up.
They must be happy.
What's wrong with you?
You seem distracted.
Did you have a fight with Cheng Qi?
Is it because of the banquet?
Did he not tell you?
The notice has been out for two days.
He didn't even mention it.
You're not really a couple.
You don't really like him.
It's okay not to go.
Yeah.
I don't like him.
I don't know how to dress up,
nor do I understand those poems.
Why should I go to the party?
Whoever wants to go can go.
You...
My Lord.
Bai is back.
You are really brother and sister.
Both are wooden.
My Lord,
we are all brothers
in the Escort Agency.
Go and live there.
Bai will teach you how to escort.
Here you are.
What's this?
It's for your previous wages.
You can't do what you want to do.
Now you want to follow you.
The Escort Agency is short of hands.
What other places offer you,
I will offer you the same.
I believe you.
Su Yuejiao,
who told you to take my IOU?
You think you can control me like this?
I tell you,
no way!
Give it back to me.
Why are you back?
I won't talk to you.
I'll go to my father for justice.
He's not good to you.
Do you want to kill him?
Why are you still like this?
You're an escort now.
Don't talk about killing all day.
Tomorrow,
remember to go to the training ground.
You're back, my dear.
Did you see
the shadow play designed by Jian?
I thought of it.
How is it?
Not bad, right?
What's wrong?
Got cheated when shopping?
Let me see.
My dear,
this dress
doesn't quite fit you.
I think the escort uniform suits you best.
Yeah.
It doesn't fit me.
I only look good in the escort uniform.
Why did you suddenly think of buying this?
It's from Bai.
What?
That Bai Yanli,
the ingrate, has come back?
You let him come back?
When do I need your permission?
Why don't you?
I'm your husband.
You're my wife.
It's a contract.
Temporary.
Fake.
I'm not as self-righteous as you.
I don't care about your business.
I...
Something's wrong.
We'd better go.
Hurry up.
I said no.
How can you refuse?
I don't want to go.
Even your brother has come around.
Why are you still so stubborn?
You and my brother,
you two are in love.
What am I to Cheng Qi?
You're doing this for the agency?
What do you mean?
The guests are all dignitaries in Yunjing.
Knowing you're Cheng Qi's wife,
they'll support the business.
Really?
You did it for the business last time.
I did it for the business.
Exactly.
Go back and get ready.
Mr. Cheng,
Why are you here alone?
Where's your wife?
Wife?
Mr. Cheng, you have a unique taste.
You know, Mr. Cheng is a live-in son-in-law.
Unlike you and me,
whose wives are noble and elegant.
Most escorts are rough and rude.
Mr. Cheng, you must have been bullied
in the escort agency, right?
My wife treats me very well.
No bullying at all.
She just
doesn't like this kind of occasion.
Do you dislike me bringing you out?
This...
Is this the attire of the Cheng family?
How can you come to the banquet
in such shabby clothes?
Is Mr. Cheng stingy
or just inexperienced?
Why are you here?
Can't I come?
Or
you think I'm embarrassing?
No.
You said you didn't like coming here.
You didn't ask.
How do you know I don't like it?
OK, my fault.
Thank you for coming here with me.
I didn't come for you.
You're really henpecked.
Not as heroic as
your poems.
Mr. Ling,
you don't know what respect means.
Thank you for the compliment.
I've had a headache these days.
My husband
bought me a lot of bird's nest
and shark fin,
saying it would nourish me.
I've gained so much weight
that I can't even fit into my hairpin.
My dear,
it's quite a coincidence.
I'm weak,
so my husband
bought me deer antlers and ginseng.
Look,
it's causing me to get all heated up.
Your husbands are so thoughtful,
Unlike my husband,
who only buys me jewelry.
He doesn't care
about anything else.
In my opinion,
Lady Cheng is unique.
Dressing like a constable,
truly eye-opening.
This is clearly a gathering of scholars.
Being late is one thing,
But this outfit and behavior,
it's truly unprecedented.
Mr. Cheng's talent
must be forced out, right?
Don't you think?
My wife is different from you ladies,
who can only rely on your husbands.
Like sparrows confined within a boudoir.
How can sparrows know the ambitions of swans?
It's normal
not to have seen it.
What does he mean?
Say something!
I'm a canary, aren't I?
Shut up.
You are invited here today
to express my gratitude.
The Starry Night Auction
was a success because of you.
We are honored
to be selected for the final.
We don't need your gratitude.
How's the money going?
My lord,
it's on its way.
It'll be here on time,
I promise.
But...
Speak.
I've been escorting goods lately,
and the Su's Escort Agency
is stealing my business.
My lord, don't get me wrong.
I'm not asking for money.
My dad and I are thinking about
merging with them.
So we can help you in the future.
Don't lose the forest for the trees.
Understood.
Thank you, my lord.
To be honest,
Mr. Ling's poetry
is well-crafted.
and worth learning from.
You're too kind.
Mr. Cheng's work is more commendable.
The Starry Gathering is full of talent.
This banquet
is also thanks to Ms. Zhang's support.
Don't you think?
Without the support of the Grand Preceptor and Ms. Zhang,
we wouldn't be here.
It's my duty.
I hope both of you
can show your best in the final.
Thanks for your good wishes.
Don't you think
Miss Zhang
is treating Mr. Cheng differently?
Just now,
Miss Zhang was
always concerned about him.
Yeah.
Mr. Cheng is so talented.
Is Miss Zhang helping him
because she has a crush on you?
Ms. Zhang is the best
in appearance,
family background,
and property
in the entire Yun State.
A beauty matches a talent.
If I were you,
I would also want to marry her.
Would I
still stick to that vulgar escort?
That's right.
You, you...
My lady,
what happened?
What's going on?
Yeah.
I want to eat fruits.
Do you want some?
Watch out!
My lady.
My wife is very strong.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Since you like fruits,
I'll have someone pick more.
No need.
I'm sorry for being rude.
I'm sorry.
I should go back to the escort agency.
Goodbye.
Miss
I'm really worried about my wife going home alone.
I'll make it up to you another day.
You can't drink,
why do you force yourself?
You...
Do you think
I've embarrassed you?
No, I don't.
I just think
you're amazing today.
You scared those ladies
to run away.
It's so satisfying.
Then...
Then why did you help Zhang Xiayun?
Do you think
I'm not as good as her?
So she's been jealous all along.
Silly girl.
In my heart,
you are the best.
Who is the best?
Su Yuejiao is the best.
Good for you.
You are the best, too.
Then I'll help you with your lines.
You said it.
You can't go back on your word.
Su's Escort Agency always keeps its word.
Okay.
Don't forget it when you wake up tomorrow.
Don't worry. I won't forget.